Repository Structure. The repository is organized as a production monorepo with shared Java libraries, Spring Boot services, a Next.js frontend, Docker and Kubernetes infrastructure, scripts, tests, and
Frontend Architecture. The frontend uses Next.js App Router, public marketing pages, authenticated app routes, a shared workspace layout, reusable UI components, API clients, hooks, and Zustand stores.
Backend Services. The backend is split into identity, foundation, audience, content, campaign, delivery, tracking, automation, deliverability, and platform services. Each service owns a domain bound
Shared Libraries. Shared libraries centralize common models, security, Kafka, cache, and test support so service code uses consistent response, tenant, event, and testing primitives.
API And Context. APIs use the /api/v1 base path. Protected requests carry tenant, workspace, environment, and request identifiers. Auth endpoints and public tracking endpoints have different contex
Data Layer. PostgreSQL stores transactional service data through Flyway migrations. ClickHouse supports analytics, Redis supports fast state, OpenSearch supports search, and MinIO handles obje
Kafka Flows. Kafka decouples signup, bootstrap, audience resolution, campaign send, delivery results, tracking ingestion, workflow execution, deliverability feedback, search, notification, and
Local Runtime. Local development starts infrastructure with Docker Compose, builds Java with Maven wrapper, runs Spring services, starts the Next.js frontend, and validates with smoke and e2e tes
Cloud Runtime. Cloud setup builds images, pushes to a registry, applies Kubernetes manifests, injects secrets and config maps, then monitors health, logs, rollouts, and service metrics.
Quality And Roadmap. The future roadmap should add OpenAPI generation, Helm and Terraform, richer observability, CI/CD, enterprise identity, visual regression testing, AI recommendations, and stronger